<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<animes>
    <anime id="001">
    <title>Bleach</title>
    <totalEpisodes>366</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicBleach.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>A high school boy named Ichigo Kurosaki has the special ability 
        to see spirits has his life completely turned around when he a girl 
        named Rukia.  Rukia is a soul reaper whose job is to allow souls 
        from the world of the living to a place called the Soul Society.  
        She does this by fighting lost souls called hollows that consume other 
        people’s souls.  However, Rukia becomes severely injured after trying 
        to save Ichigo from a hollow she was fighting.  Now Ichigo is left to 
        fight this hollow before it consumes Ichigo’s soul.</summary>
    </anime>
    <anime id="002">
    <title>Death Note</title>
    <totalEpisodes>37</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Detective Fiction, Psychological Thriller, Supernatural</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicDeathNote.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>Light Yagami is a teenage genius that finds a book called 
        “Death Note”.  The book claims that if a name is written then that 
        person will die.  Light test this claim finding out that it is indeed 
        true.  He then meet the Death Note’s previous owner a death god named 
        Ryuk.  Light understanding the power he has starts to kill all the 
        criminals in the world until there are only good people left on this 
        earth.</summary>
    </anime>
    <anime id="003">
    <title>Mobile Suit Gundam SEED Destiny</title>
    <totalEpisodes>50</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Mecha, Military</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicGundam.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>Set two years after the show Mobile Suit Gundam SEED, the show 
        follows a new character named Shinn Asuka a soldier from ZAFT. ZAFT 
        is a group of humans who are genetically enhanced at birth.  ZAFT is 
        about to enter into another war against the regular human race, the 
        Naturals as Shin is preparing to fight.</summary>
    </anime>
    <anime id="004">
    <title>Clannad After Story</title>
    <totalEpisodes>23</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Romance, Tragedy</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicClannad.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>Tomoya is high school student who hates his life.  When he was 
        young his mother passed away causing his father to get into alcohol 
        and gambling to ease the pain.  This intern effects into becoming 
        delinquent.  However one day he meets a girl named Nagisa and 
        befriends her, with his life starts to change for the better.</summary>
    </anime>
    <anime id="005">
    <title>Full Metal Alchemist</title>
    <totalEpisodes>51</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Adventure, Science Fantasy</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicFMA.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>Brothers Edward and Alphonse Elric attempt to revive their dead 
        mother back to life.  However things don’t go very bad and they both 
        lose their bodies.  They are now made of machine and trying to find 
        the philosopher’s stone to obtain their bodies. </summary>
    </anime>
    <anime id="006">
    <title>Fruit Basket</title>
    <totalEpisodes>26</totalEpisodes>
    <genre>Fantasy, Romance</genre>
    <imgSrc>../images/animePicFruitBasket.png</imgSrc>
    <summary>Tohru Honda is an orphan girl who is fortunate enough to find a 
        home with the Sohma family.  But she quickly learns that family is 
        possessed by the 12 animals of the zodiac and have been cursed to 
        turn into their animal forms when they are embraced by anyone of 
        the opposite sex.</summary>
    </anime>
</animes>